A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaign Files, Presidential, 1958-1968; 2; 6.8 Cubic Feet 18 document boxes
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Resurrection City Statement (Proposed), undated (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Statement on General Eisenhower for possible Future Release, 1968 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 750)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, "The Case for Nelson Rockefeller" Geo Gilder Draft, undated (Box 69, Folder 751)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Vietnam Speech (Draft Idea), 1968 June 28 (Box 69, Folder 752)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Internal Relations Council, 1968 July 16 (Box 69, Folder 753)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Education Department at Cabinet Level, 1968 May 27 (Box 69, Folder 754)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Farmland Preservation Statement, 1968 May 25 (Box 69, Folder 755)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, "Achieving Domestic Peace in America", 1968 July 22 (Box 69, Folder 756)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Anti-Humphrey Speech, 1968 July 22 (Box 69, Folder 757)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Policy Paper on the Great Society, 1968 July 22 (Box 69, Folder 758)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, "Racial Peace", 1968 July 22 (Box 69, Folder 759)
- Campaign Files, 1970 Gubernatorial, 3; 3.6 Cubic Feet 10 document boxes
  This subseries contains campaign literature, National Media Analysis reports, press releases, and election statistics on Rockefeller's 1970 gubernatorial campaign.
  - Ad Agencies Campaign, 1969 March 25-1970 August 31 (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Arts and Culture, 1970 April 30-September 24 (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Bills for Campaign, 1970 April-August (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - Candidates List, 1970 October 9 (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - Celebrities for Nelson Rockefeller, 1970 September 2 (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - Cities, 1970 March 30-June 19 (Box 69, Folder 765)
  - Commercials, Critical Correspondence, 1970 July 8-August 24 (Box 69, Folder 766)
  - Commercials and Radio and TV Schedule, 1970 August 8-November 1 (Box 69, Folder 767)
  - Commercials Summary Report of Group Sessions on Eight Televison Commercial Concepts, 1970 July (Box 69, Folder 768)
  - Commercials, Verbatim Questionnaire, and Answers, Eight Television Commercial Concepts, 1970 July (Box 70, Folder 769)
  - Commercials, Reports on Second Series of Group Sessions on Television and Radio Concepts, 1970 August (Box 70, Folder 770)
  - Commercials, Radio and Television (Tinker Correspondence), 1970 June 4-October 5 (Box 70, Folder 771)
  - Communications Department, General, 1970 May 13-June 16 (Box 70, Folder 772)
  - Congressional Race, 1970 January 29-July 2 (Box 70, Folder 773)
  - Consumer Protection Board, Betty Furness, 1970 August 10-October 5 (Box 70, Folder 774)
  - Constitutional Amendments on Ballot, 1969 November 4 (Box 70, Folder 775)
  - County Fair Messages, 1970 June 12-26 (Box 70, Folder 776)
  - Day Care Centers, 1970 April (Box 70, Folder 777)
  - Debates and Interviews, Scheduled and Pending, 1970 March 11-October 15 (Box 70, Folder 778)
  - Debates and Strategies, Firm Dates, 1970 July 13-October 26 (Box 70, Folder 779)
  - Democrats, Miscellaneous, 1969 April 18-1970 October 15 (Box 71, Folder 780)
  - Democrats, Rosenman for Nelson Rockefeller, 1970 March 19-October 22 (Box 71, Folder 781)
  - Democratic Convention at Grossingers: Some Sights and Sounds, undated (Box 71, Folder 782)
  - Education, Miscellaneous, 1970 January 28-September 3 (Box 71, Folder 783)
  - Endorsements, 1970 May 19-November 2 (Box 71, Folder 784)
  - Ethnic, Miscellaneous, 1970 January 26-October 2 (Box 71, Folder 785)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 August 3-November 9 (Box 71, Folder 786)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 March 3-July 29 (Box 71, Folder 787)
  - General Correspondence, 1969 May 5-1970 February 27 (Box 71, Folder 788)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, Campaign for Governor, 1970 March 19-October 23 (Box 71, Folder 789)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, (Lifted) Stolen Statements and Schedules, 1970 September 25-October 2 (Box 72, Folder 790)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, (Lifted) Stolen Statements and Schedules, 1970 June 9-September 24 (Box 72, Folder 791)
  - Gulay, Lou, Public Relations, 1970 July 13-October 12 (Box 72, Folder 793)
  - Ideas, Favorite Letters for Possible Public Use, 1970 July 20-October 22 (Box 72, Folder 794)
  - Inflation Memo, 1970 February 25 (Box 72, Folder 795)
  - Invitations and Schedules, 1970 May 9-September 17 (Box 72, Folder 796)
  - Issues, Major Issues Booklet, 1969 December 17-February 7 (Box 72, Folder 797)
  - Italian Vote, 1970 May 11-October 7 (Box 72, Folder 798)
  - Jewish Vote, 1970 April 3-October 6 (Box 72, Folder 799)
  - Jewish Consituents, Martin Burstein Activities, 1970 January 11-October 19 (Box 72, Folder 800)
  - Kendrick, Thomas, Speech Material, 1970 June (Box 73, Folder 801)
  - Labor, 1970 June 1-October 20 (Box 73, Folder 802)
  - Law Enforcement, 1970 July 14-October 2 (Box 73, Folder 803)
  - Leibowitz, Samuel, Endorsement of Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 October 7-19 (Box 73, Folder 804)
  - Leonard, Frank, Nixon Campaign, 1968 December 19, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 805)
  - Lindsay, John, Mayor, 1969 October 29-1970 November 9 (Box 73, Folder 806)
  - Campaign Literature, 1970 July 21-September 17 (Box 73, Folder 807)
  - Campaign Literature, 1970 March 30-May 25 (Box 73, Folder 808)
  - Lothian, John, (Information Material Press) Pamphlets on Drugs and Syphilis, 1969 February 17-April 15 (Box 73, Folder 809)
  - National Media Analysis, Correspondence, 1969 November 15-1970 December 7 (Box 73, Folder 810)
  - National Media Analysis, County Profile (Polls), 1970 April 3-September 11 (Box 73, Folder 811)
  - National Media Analysis, Weekly Reports, 1970 September 1-October 26 (Box 74, Folder 812)
  - National Media Analysis, Weekly Reports, 1970 June 30-August 31 (Box 74, Folder 813)
  - National Media Analysis, Weekly Reports, 1970 April 28-June 29 (Box 74, Folder 814)
  - National Media Analysis, Weekly Reports, 1970 February 10-April 27 (Box 74, Folder 815)
  - National Media Analysis, Special Trend Reports, 1970 January 27-July 6 (Box 74, Folder 816)
  - Negroes, Support of Governor, 1970 April 3-October 21 (Box 74, Folder 817)
  - Newspaper Clipping of Interest, 1970 January 6-October 8 (Box 74, Folder 818)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting, 1958 August 25-1970 March 24 (Box 74, Folder 819)
  - Organization of Campaign, 1969 June 17-1970 May 19 (Box 74, Folder 820)
  - Photos, Photo Session Correspondence, 1970 June 23-September 24 (Box 75, Folder 821)
  - Photos, "A Day in the Life of Nelson Rockefeller" (Bob Wands), undated (Box 75, Folder 822)
  - New York City, Press Releases, 1970 June 9-September 23 (Box 75, Folder 823)
  - Platform Committee (New York State Republican Hearings), 1970 February 5-March 23 (Box 75, Folder 824)
  - Press (Correspondence, Releases, Press Office), 1970 March 31-October 30 (Box 75, Folder 825)
  - Press Releases, Campaign, 1970 June 25-July 31 (Box 75, Folder 826)
  - Press Releases, Campaign, 1970 August 2-September 30 (Box 75, Folder 827)
  - Press Releases, Campaign, 1970 October (Box 75, Folder 828)
  - Puerto Ricans, Flood Telethon, 1969 April 25-1970 October 14 (Box 75, Folder 829)
  - Questions and Answers for Nelson Rockefeller, 1970 July 16-October 26 (Box 75, Folder 830)
  - Regan, Edward V., Candidate for State Comptroller, 1970 April 1-September 27 (Box 75, Folder 831)
  - Republican State Committee News Releases, 1970 March 26-October 10 (Box 75, Folder 832)
  - Resumes, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 833)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1970 July 8-October 21 (Box 76, Folder 834)
    Conditions Governing Access
  - Speakers Bureau, 1969 August 13-1970 February 16 (Box 76, Folder 835)
  - Speeches/or Scripts For Tapes, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 836)
  - Tapings, 1970 September 28 (Box 76, Folder 837)
  - Materials for Book by Nelson Rockefeller on Governorship, 1970 May 19-1974 October 6 (Box 76, Folder 838)
  - Materials for Book by Nelson Rockefeller on Governorship, 1968 January 21-1969 October 17 (Box 76, Folder 839)
  - Materials for Book by Nelson Rockefeller on Governorship, 1962 July 4-1967 November 2 (Box 76, Folder 840)
  - Materials for Book by Nelson Rockefeller on Governorship, 1957 September 23-1960 November 29 (Box 76, Folder 841)
  - Materials for Book by Nelson Rockefeller on Governorship, Supplemental Material, Annual Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 76, Folder 842)
  - Election Results by NY County, 1964-1972 (Box 77, Folder 843)
  - Election Results Originals, Gubernatorial and Presidential, 1958-1972 (Box 77, Folder 844)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1965-1970 (Box 77, Folder 845)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1965-1970 (Box 77, Folder 846)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1966-1967 1970 (Box 77, Folder 847)
  - Election Statistics, National, 1967-1970 (Box 77, Folder 848)
  - Election Statistics, National, 1968-1970 (Box 77, Folder 849)
  - Election Statistics, National, 1968-1970 (Box 78, Folder 850)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 851)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1971-1971 (Box 78, Folder 852)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 853)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 854)
  - Election Statistics, State, 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 855)
  - Enrollment and Election Figures, Working Sheets (by County), 1958-1971 (Box 78, Folder 856)
  - Photographs (Box 78A)
- Speech Transcripts, 1971-1974; 4; 4.4 Cubic Feet 12 document boxes
  These transcripts are of Rockefeller's remarks and statements given throughout the country during his last term as Governor of New York.
  - Important Transcripts: New York State Citizens Committee for Revenue Sharing, 1971 June 18 (Box 79, Folder 857)
  - Important Transcripts: "Here and Now" WNET-TV (Housing), 1971 June 29 (Box 79, Folder 858)
  - Important Transcripts: T.V. Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller by David Frost, 1971 July 20 (Box 79, Folder 859)
  - Important Transcripts: Testimony of Nelson A. Rockefeller at Senator Muskie Hearing, 1971 August 3 (Box 79, Folder 860)
  - Press Release, 1972 January 4-February 28 (Box 79, Folder 861)
  - Press Release, 1972 March 1-30 (Box 79, Folder 862)
  - Press Release, 1972 April 1-28 (Box 79, Folder 863)
  - Press Release, 1972 May 1-25 (Box 79, Folder 864)
  - Press Release, 1972 June 1-30 (Box 79, Folder 865)
  - Press Release, 1972 July 1-29 (Box 79, Folder 866)
  - Press Release, 1972 August 1-31 (Box 79, Folder 867)
  - Press Release, 1972 September 6-30 (Box 79, Folder 868)
  - Press Release, 1972 October 2-31 (Box 79, Folder 869)
  - Press Release, 1972 November 1-December 31 (Box 79, Folder 870)
  - Important Transcripts, 1972 July 27-October 31 (Box 79, Folder 871)
  - Press Release, 1973 January 2-February 28 (Box 79, Folder 872)
  - Press Release, 1973 March 1-April 25 (Box 80, Folder 873)
  - Press Release, 1973 May 2-June 30 (Box 80, Folder 874)
  - Press Release, 1973 July 1-August 28 (Box 80, Folder 875)
  - Press Release, 1973 September 5-October 31 (Box 80, Folder 876)
  - Press Release, 1973 November 5-December 11 (Box 80, Folder 877)
  - Remarks and Questions at Republican Committee Luncheon, 1973 January 8 (Box 80, Folder 878)
  - Meeting of Nelson A. Rockefeller with Council of Agricultural Organizations of New York State, 1973 January 8 (Box 80, Folder 879)
  - Press questions at Cafeteria Opening at Legislative Building, Albany, 1973 January 9 (Box 80, Folder 880)
  - Remarks at First Panel Sheriff's Jury Dinner, 1973 January 11 (Box 80, Folder 881)
  - Remarks at Farewell Dinner for Ambassador Rabin, State of Israel Bonds, 1973 January 11 (Box 80, Folder 882)
  - Remarks at Deter Brennan Reception, 1973 January 12 (Box 80, Folder 883)
  - Budget School at the Executive Mansion, Albany, NY, 1973 January 14 (Box 80, Folder 884)
  - Remarks at the New York Press Club, 1973 January 17 (Box 80, Folder 885)
  - News Conference Red Room, State Capital, Albany, 1973 January 22 (Box 80, Folder 886)
  - New York State Veterans of Foreign Wars Legislative Dinner, Albany, 1973 January 22 (Box 80, Folder 887)
  - News Conference in the Red Room, State Capital, Albany, 1973 January 23 (Box 80, Folder 888)
  - Remarks at Annual Dinner of the Westchester County Committee, 1973 January 25 (Box 80, Folder 889)
  - Remarks at American Legion Legislative Dinner, 1973 January 29 (Box 80, Folder 890)
  - Testimony Before the Joint Hearing of the Senate and Assembly Codes Commission, Albany, NY, 1973 January 30 (Box 80, Folder 891)
  - New York State Legislative Forum, Albany, NY, 1973 February 6 (Box 80, Folder 892)
  - Remarks Association of Towns Meeting, New York City, 1973 February 6 (Box 80, Folder 893)
  - Remarks at the Association of Fire Districts, New York City, 1973 February 6 (Box 80, Folder 894)
  - Remarks of Nelson A. Rockefeller at the Empire State Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Albany, NY, 1973 February 6 (Box 81, Folder 895)
  - Remarks at the Lincoln Day Dinner, Chicago, IL, 1973 February 9 (Box 81, Folder 896)
  - Signing of No-Fault Automobile Insurance Bill, Albany, 1970 February 13 (Box 81, Folder 897)
  - U.S. Senate Sub-Committee on Constitutional Rights, Washington DC, 1973 February 22 (Box 81, Folder 898)
  - Joint Session of the West Virginia State Legislature, Charleston, WV, 1973 February 22 (Box 81, Folder 899)
  - Tribute to Winthrop Rockefeller, Petit Jean Mountain Arkansas, 1973 March 4 (Box 81, Folder 900)
  - Remarks at New York State AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, Albany New York City, 1973 March 5 (Box 81, Folder 901)
  - Remarks at League of Women's Voters, Albany, NY, 1973 March 6 (Box 81, Folder 902)
  - Remarks at Republican State Committee Meeting, Albany, NY, 1973 March 6 (Box 81, Folder 903)
  - Remarks at the New York State Broadcasters Association, Albany, 1973 March 6 (Box 81, Folder 904)
  - Remarks at the Women's National Republican Club, New York City, 1973 March 10 (Box 81, Folder 905)
  - Remarks at Distinguished Service Awards Ceremony, State University, 1972 March 13 (Box 81, Folder 906)
  - Remarks at Governor Dunn's Annual Prayer Breakfast, Nashville, TN, 1973 March 22 (Box 81, Folder 907)
  - Remarks at the Europe-American Conference, Amsterdam, 1973 March 26 (Box 81, Folder 908)
  - Remarks at the Emma Willard School, Troy, NY, 1973 April 2 (Box 81, Folder 909)
  - Remarks at the Judge for the Court of Appeals CSEA Strike, NY, 1973 April 3 (Box 81, Folder 910)
  - Remarks at World Trade Center Dedication, NY, 1973 April 4 (Box 81, Folder 911)
  - Remarks at Commerce and Industry Association, NY, 1973 April 4 (Box 81, Folder 912)
  - Remarks at the New York State Republican Committee Youth Conference, Albany, 1973 April 9 (Box 81, Folder 913)
  - Remarks at America's Third Century Lecture, Montana, 1973 April 13 (Box 81, Folder 914)
  - Remarks at New Haven Inaugural Ceremony, Stamford, CT, 1973 April 16 (Box 81, Folder 915)
  - Remarks at Virginia State Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Norfolk, VA, 1973 April 18 (Box 81, Folder 916)
  - Remarks at the American Arbitration Association, NY, 1973 April 19 (Box 81, Folder 917)
  - Remarks at the Dinner Honoring Prime Minister Giulio Andreotti of Italy, 1973 April 19 (Box 81, Folder 918)
  - News Conference Red Room, State Capital, Albany, 1973 April 26 (Box 81, Folder 919)
  - Remarks for the Freedom Foundation Honoring Dr. Frank Stanton, NY Hilton, 1973 April 26 (Box 81, Folder 920)
  - Remarks at the Society of the Silurians Annual Dinner, NY, 1973 May 1 (Box 81, Folder 921)
  - Remarks at the Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars Conference on New Federalism, Washington, DC, 1973 May 2 (Box 81, Folder 922)
  - Remarks at the University of Virginia Legal Forum, Virginia, 1973 May 2 (Box 81, Folder 923)
  - Remarks at the Gold Medal Award to Dr. Ronan, Citizen's Budget Comm., NY, 1973 May 3 (Box 81, Folder 924)
  - Remarks at the New York Urban League Dinner Honoring Jackie Robinson, NY, 1973 May 3 (Box 81, Folder 925)
  - Remarks at the Signing of the Narcotics Bill, Red Room, Albany, 1973 May 8 (Box 81, Folder 926)
  - Appointment of Michael Armstrong as District Attorney of Queens, NY, 1973 May 9 (Box 81, Folder 927)
  - Remarks at the Kennedy Rail Link Signing, Port Authority, NY, 1973 May 10 (Box 81, Folder 928)
  - News Conference at the Republican Association, 1973 May 11 (Box 81, Folder 929)
  - Press Conference of Nelson A. Rockefeller at the White House, Washington, DC, 1973 May 14 (Box 81, Folder 930)
  - Remarks at the Election of Chairman, National Study Commission on Water Pollution Control, Washington, DC, 1973 May 15 (Box 81, Folder 931)
  - Remarks at the Award For Valor to Professor Francis H. Anderson, Red Room, Albany, 1973 May 21 (Box 81, Folder 932)
  - Signing of Bill on the Adirondack Park, Red Room, Albany, 1973 May 22 (Box 81, Folder 933)
  - Remarks at the John LaFarge Memorial Award for Interracial Justice, NY, 1973 May 24 (Box 81, Folder 934)
  - Remarks Testimonial Dinner for Governor McCall, Portland, Oregon, 1973 June 4 (Box 82, Folder 935)
  - Remarks at the National Governor's Conference, Lake Tahoe, Nevada, 1973 June 4 (Box 82, Folder 936)
  - Remarks at the Governor's Labor Reception, New York City, 1973 June 12 (Box 82, Folder 937)
  - Remarks at the New York Republican State Committee Luncheon, NY, 1973 June 14 (Box 82, Folder 938)
  - Remarks at Annual State Committee Luncheon, NY, 1973 June 14 (Box 82, Folder 939)
  - Remarks Bill Signing of New York State Sports Authority, NY, 1973 June 14 (Box 82, Folder 940)
  - Remarks Summit County Republican, Akron, Ohio, 1973 June 20 (Box 82, Folder 941)
  - Remarks at the New York State Broadcasters Association, Cooperstown, NY, 1973 July 17 (Box 82, Folder 942)
  - Press Briefing held at 55th Street, New York City, 1973 July 18 (Box 82, Folder 943)
  - Press Conference held at 55th Street, New York City, 1973 July 20 (Box 82, Folder 944)
  - Questions following Meeting of City Officials, New York City, 1973 July 24 (Box 82, Folder 945)
  - Briefing of Legislators on the Transportation Bond Issue, Albany, NY, 1973 July 27 (Box 82, Folder 946)
  - Swearing in Ceremony of the New State Racing and Wagering Board, New York City, 1973 August 7 (Box 82, Folder 947)
  - Press Questions following Ceremony at Harlem River State Park, Bronx, 1973 August 15 (Box 82, Folder 948)
  - Remarks at the American Political Science Association, New Orleans, LA, 1973 September 5 (Box 82, Folder 949)
  - Remarks at New York State AFL-CIO Convention, Concord Hotel, 1973 September 6 (Box 82, Folder 950)
  - Drug Law Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller on the "Today's Show", NBC, 1973 September 7 (Box 82, Folder 951)
  - Remarks at Swearing on of Judges, New York City, 1973 September 10 (Box 82, Folder 952)
  - Tape Interview of Nar and Rolland D. Headlee, Executive Director, Town Hall, Los Angeles, 1973 September 11 (Box 82, Folder 953)
  - News Interview, Biltmore Hotel, Los Angeles, 1973 September 11 (Box 82, Folder 954)
  - Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller by David Burnham, New York City, 1973 September 12 (Box 82, Folder 955)
  - Remarks at Testimonial Dinner for Charles W. Sandman, Cherry Hill, N.J., 1973 September 18 (Box 82, Folder 956)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Japanese Exchange Newsmen, New York City, 1973 September 18 (Box 82, Folder 957)
  - Remarks at Associated Industries Annual Dinner, Lake Placid, NY, 1973 September 21 (Box 82, Folder 958)
  - Remarks at the Italian-American Legislators Dinner, New York City, 1973 September 21 (Box 82, Folder 959)
  - Remarks at Project Hope Award Dinner Honoring Henry Kissinger, New York City, 1973 September 25 (Box 82, Folder 960)
  - Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller by Edie O'Neil, New York City, 1973 September 27 (Box 82, Folder 961)
  - Press Conference at Pick-Congress Hotel, Chicago, 1973 September 28 (Box 82, Folder 962)
  - Remarks of Nelson A. Rockefeller at Executives Club Luncheon, Chicago, 1973 September 29 (Box 82, Folder 963)
  - Remarks at Oakland County Republican Committee, Michigan, 1973 September 29 (Box 82, Folder 964)
  - T.V. Taping of Nelson A. Rockefeller Lou Gordon T.V. Show, Michigan, 1973 September 29 (Box 82, Folder 965)
  - Address of the MaCombe County Republican Club Dinner, Michigan, 1973 September 29 (Box 82, Folder 966)
  - Remarks at the Fund-raising for John Marchi, New York City, 1973 October 1 (Box 82, Folder 967)
  - Remarks at the Cleveland Morning Exchange T.V. Program, Ohio, 1973 October 3 (Box 82, Folder 968)
  - Press Conference at Cleveland Convention Center, Ohio, 1973 October 3 (Box 82, Folder 969)
  - Remarks at Long Island Association Breakfast, East Meadow, NY, 1973 October 9 (Box 82, Folder 970)
  - Remarks at the Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Washington DC, 1973 October 10 (Box 82, Folder 971)
  - Press Conference at 22 West 55th Office, New York City, 1973 October 10 (Box 82, Folder 972)
  - Remarks at the Westchester County Republican Comm. on Unity Reception, Rye, NY, 1973 October 12 (Box 83, Folder 973)
  - Remarks at the Dedication Ceremony of the Northern Westchester Hospital, Mt. Kisco, 1973 October 13 (Box 83, Folder 974)
  - Cabinet Meeting in the Red Room, Albany, 1973 October 16 (Box 83, Folder 975)
  - Remarks at the Jewish Theological Seminary Inauguration Ceremony, New York City, 1973 October 21 (Box 83, Folder 976)
  - Remarks at the New York State United Nations Day Observance at Rockefeller Center, NY, 1983 October 21 (Box 83, Folder 977)
  - Remarks at the New York Radio Market Broadcasters, New York City, 1973 October 23 (Box 83, Folder 978)
  - Press Conference at Phoenix Press Club, Phoenix, Arizona, 1973 October 25 (Box 83, Folder 979)
  - Remarks at the Phoenix Trunk 'N Tusk Dinner, Phoenix, Arizona, 1973 October 25 (Box 83, Folder 980)
  - T.V. Taping of Nelson A. Rockefeller at Station KVOA, Tucson, Arizona, 1973 October 26 (Box 83, Folder 981)
  - Address at the University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 1973 October 26 (Box 83, Folder 982)
  - Address at the College of Law, Arizona State University, Arizona, 1973 October 26 (Box 83, Folder 983)
  - Press Conference at Hotel Fort Des Moines, Iowa, 1973 October 30 (Box 83, Folder 984)
  - Remarks at the Iowa Republican State Central Comm. Dinner, Des Moines, Iowa, 1973 October 30 (Box 83, Folder 985)
  - Remarks at the 25th Military Academy, West Point, NY, 1973 October 31 (Box 83, Folder 986)
  - Remarks at the Northeastern Regional Conference, New York City, 1973 November 13 (Box 83, Folder 987)
  - Remarks at the Dedication Ceremonies for the New Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, New York City, 1973 November 14 (Box 83, Folder 988)
  - Remarks at the Foundation Group Luncheon, NY, 1973 November 15 (Box 83, Folder 989)
  - Remarks at the Academy of Political Science, Columbia University, NY, 1973 November 16 (Box 83, Folder 990)
  - Press Conference for the New York Subway Fare, 22 West 55th Street, Office, New York City, 1973 November 20 (Box 83, Folder 991)
  - Remarks at the Empire State Plaza Dedication, Albany, NY, 1973 November 21 (Box 83, Folder 992)
  - Remarks at the State University Trustee Luncheon 25th Anniversary SUNY, Albany, NY, 1973 November 21 (Box 83, Folder 993)